Ahh!
♪ Went down to Santa Fe
♪ Where Renoir
paints the walls ♪
♪ Described you clearly
but the sky began to fall ♪
♪ Am I ever gonna
see your face again? ♪
♪ Tram cars and taxis
like a waxworks on the move ♪
♪ Carry young girls past me
but none of them are you ♪
♪ Am I ever gonna
see your face again? ♪
see your face again?♪
♪ Without you near me
♪ I've got no place to go ♪
♪ Wait at the bar...♪
It's your last night
before you go
and you're not even
spending it at home!
Promise it's just you
and the girls tonight?
And definitely no booze!
♪ Am I ever gonna
see your face... ♪
If your
grandparents find out
you're using
the beach house for--
Penny, promise me no booze
and definitely no smoking
like last year.
I'm just
nervous of Katrina!
Katrina. I don't trust her.
You know I trust you and the
girls, but your cousin just...
Well, she invited herself.
As if we want her here.
Why would she invite herself?
How'd she even
get out here, anyway?
Hmm.
I'm serious.
You should ring me
if there's any rubbish.
I swear to God,
if she contacts you
when you start uni...
Jesus, Mum, you gotta relax.
She's just a dickhead.
What's the worst she could do?
Okay, love you.
Love you too, love.
Have a good time.
Thank you.
Hi, Toni!
Girls, be good.
We're always good.
Yeah, right!
- Bye!
- See ya.
Love you.
Oh, piss off.
Oh, school's out.
Our youth has gone.
We're literally so old.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
You're a terrible liar.
Have you heard back
from the unis?
You're officially looking at
the world's biggest loser.
They allsaid no?
Are you kidding?
You applied for--
Anything I thought would take
me. Even advertising said no.
That's crazy.
Don't tell Penny.
This dog's got no future.
Keepin' it!
- Oh, you're all so grown up.
- Mum!
I'll be back in the morning
to make breakfast.
- Thanks, Jen.
Amy. Tiger.
Toni.
Oh, bye, my darling. Ohh!
Okay.
- Okay, thanks, Mum!
- Love you.
- Bye.
- Bye. Bye, bye, bye. Bye.
- Bye!
Cute.
Hey.
You've never been a loser.
Mm.
I need to talk to you.
Amy, we're gonna
get the booze.
Okay.
Fuckin' love this shed.
Yeah, well, it's not
going anywhere.
How come we haven't
talked all week?
Sorry.
Did you tell Amy
that we kissed?
Nah.
I mean, she's our friend.
It's not a secret, is it?
So... we're good?
Yeah. We're always
fuckin' good.
Well, well, well!
- I knew you'd turn up.
- Yeah.
Last night at the beach house
and we're not invited?
That's, uh...
What's that, Nick?
- That's bullshit, Josh.
- Yeah, that's bullshit.
Ah, it's a no-dick event.
How come you're invited,
then, Big Balls?
Aw, I forgot
how funny you are.
No, you didn't.
Ooh!
You know what I want.
Well, you know, we, uh,
heard a bit of a rumour.
Oh, he's on fire tonight.
Wine?
That's a little bit fancy.
You gonna come back
and visit us, Penny?
Yeah.
What about you?
You goin' to college?
Nah. Didn't really apply.
Yeah, nah, same here.
Can't all be fuckin' heroes.
Guess not.
Do you need help
with that, Penny?
Think I got it.
Mmm, that's good.
Catch ya.
See ya, Penny.
Fuckin' told you, dude.
Oh, my God. That's hot!
They turned into lesbians!
Can't all be fuckin' heroes.
Excuse me,
Miss University Law Student,
Miss Perfect
Everyone Loves You--
Everyone?
Shut up.
Okay, I'm gonna say it
because you're a chicken
and I'm not.
What?
You should come with me.
As if.
Stay at the place
that Mum got me.
It's one bedroom, if that's
alright. Or don't you wanna?
Mm, what would I do?
I dunno.
Be my equally
hot and cool girlfriend.
That's basically
a full-time job.
Are you serious?
Is that a yes?
It's a yes!
Whoo!
Why is Kat here?
I didn't think she'd turn up.
Oh, shit.
You're 'dog'.
'Fat'.
I was fat for one year
when Dad left.
Here you go, 'slut'.
Bloody lawyer in the family.
Mm-mm-mm!
Mm-hm.
Mm, mm.
Mm-mm!
Hmm.
You girls in for a good night?
He looks
like a rock star.
He's got, like, six pairs
of leather pants.
His family's got
all these, like,
nightclubs on King Street.
Heaps of famous people go
and, like, we get
free drink cards,
like, the second we step in.
All the security guards
know my name.
It's pretty fuckin' sick.
You should see
his friends, though.
Old men.
One of them's, like, 40.
- That's disgusting.
- My dad's 40.
Yeah, well, once you go old,
you don't go back.
Ugh.
The only thing
is, though...
...is the grey pubes.
Men, real men,
know what they're doing,
if you know what I mean.
Finger-banged me
in the back of a car
the other day at a festival.
Drove me nuts.
He hasn't got his
licence back, though, yet.
It's been, like, six weeks
since he got out.
- So his mate had to drive--
- Out?
- Wait. From jail?
- Fuckin' classic.
Wait. Why was he in jail?
He doesn't like
to talk about it.
Yeah, but do you know?
I said he doesn't like
to talk about it.
But did he tell you?
How do I go about that, Amy?
Well, you could tell him
about Year 12,
when you stalked Nick
and got expelled
and then he put
the restraining order on you
and you broke it, so then you
had to do community service.
I mean,
that was really serious
and everyone
hated you for ages.
- Do you remember what Josh--
- Shh.
That was bullshit.
That--
I forgot he even existed.
You guys aren't still
friends with them, are you?
Surely not.
Oh, you're kidding. Fuck!
They're still doing the summer
job at the bottle-o, hey?
Right?
Losers! Fuckin'...
I'm going for a piss.
"Finger-banged me
in the back of the car! Uh!"
Oh!
Sorry, guys.
Fat head.
Mmm!
Guys, I feel fucked.
Oh, Penny!
-  Penny!
-  Are you okay?
-  Hey, Penny?
-  I'm okay.
-  Should we call Jen?
-  Don't call my mum.
If she sees me like this,
I'm dead.
What the fuck?
-  Whatever.
-  Come on. Just lie down.
It's okay.
Maybe it was
something you ate.
Oh, my fuckin' God!
- You drugged the cupcakes.
- Oh!
Genius.
- All of them?
- No, just Barbie.
Come on. Good girl!
Fuck.
It'd take
a horse tranquilliser
to knock you out, Ames.
-  Oh, my God.
- They're just pills.
She'll be fine!
-  Don't call anyone!
- I'm calling an ambulance!
No! They'll call the cops.
Fuckin' drug record,
marijuana in her system,
underage drinking...
Bye-bye, lawyer,
and hello, police record.
Toni, please!
My mum said you can't even
be a cop
if you do drugs anymore.
Mmm, Toni,
don't ruin her life.
Just fuckin' relax, you moll.
I chug 'em, like, every night.
And they said she couldn't
take a bad photo.
Ooh!
Alright, let's have some fun.
You. Can you
put the bong in her hand?
- Get the fuck out!
- Oh, come on!
Bitches like her only have
fuckin' dog friends
to make her look hotter.
I'm literally giving you
your only chance
to get back at her,
so fuckin' take your chance!
Get back at her
for what?
For a lifetime of making us
feel like fucking losers.
Get out!
- Ah-oww!
- Get... out!
Are you trying to kick me
out of myfamily's
holiday house right now, Toni?
Don't you ever
go near her again.
Oh, my God...
Fucking, it's over.
School's out, dog!
We finally got rid of you.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
The fuckin' princess and lezzo
would ride off
into the sunrise together?
You're a fuckin' psycho cunt!
She never gave
a fuck about you
and now the mangy fuckin' dog
goes back to where
it fuckin' belongs.
I am the stray dog
they let in, but guess what.
They still love me
more than you.
Your family hate you 'cause
you're a dirty fuckin' lesbian
so you stole mine
and turned them against me!
And your family hate you
'cause you're fuckin' crazy.
-  That's true.
- Fuck off, Amy!
But it is!
You've always been awful, Kat.
No-one knows why.
You two are so fucked.
Fuckin' bitches.
Hi.
Can you come get me?
Please, you owe me. Please.
Okay.
Yes, now.
♪ Watch a horror movie
right there on my TV ♪
♪ Horror movie right there
on my TV ♪
♪ Horror movie
right there on my TV ♪
♪ Shockin' me
right outta my brain ♪
♪ Shockin' me right outta
my brain ♪
♪ Watch a horror movie
right there on my TV ♪
♪ Horror movie
♪ Horror movie...♪
-  Thank God.
- Yep.
Toni.
Shit.
Toni?
Quick. Get her in the bedroom.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Quick!
Come on, come on, come on.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
Quick, quick.
Stop.
Quick.
- Wait here.
- Toni, don't!
-  What?
- Need to use my phone.
Bullshit. Just leave.
Hello, sweetheart.
That's Angus, the one
I was telling you about.
My boyfriend.
Yeah, I don't mind
picking her up,
but this place is in the
middle of butt-fuck nowhere
and now we're running
really late,
so I've just gotta make
a quick call.
Ooh. Here is...
Here.
It's 40 cents for the call.
Come on, Toni.
Just open my door.
Leave.
I don't think
she likes me.
You're so scary.
- Just let us in!
-  Shut up, dickhead.
- Fuck you.
-  That's Rodowsky.
And the big dog...
Well, that's Merrick.
He doesn't bite, but...
Look, we just need
to use your dunny.
- Just piss in the garden.
- I can't piss in the garden.
Does this look like a piss?
I'm gonna shit myself!
- I'm touching fuckin' cloth.
-  Don't!
Don't open it!
I don't wanna be the cunt
of the party, alright?
But we gotta
get somewhere fast
and this little pick-up
has made us really late, okay?
Now, look, I'm normally a
really top bloke, sweetheart.
Yeah?
But I fuckin' hate being late.
So if you don't open
this fuckin' door
and let us make
a fuckin' call,
then we are gonna have
a fuckin' problem, okay?
Wait!
Fuckin' took your time.
Move, move,
move, move, move! Move!
Fuckin' get outta the
fuckin'-- Where's the dunny?
Fuckin' dumb...
Sorry for the wait, boys.
Oh, smile!
Oh, you bitch!
Hmm.
Huh.
You right?
Yeah, I'm good. And you?
- You out here on your own?
-  No.
Um, Penny's mum and my mum
are both coming back
in the morning.
- Penny?
- No, that's Toni.
Penny's asleep in the bedroom.
I'm Amy--
Shut it!
You're a tough cookie,
aren't ya?
Can be.
You remind me of someone.
I thought you were
running late.
Stay here, smart-arse.
Oh, Toni,
I am so sorry.
This is really bad.
You idiot.
- Did you make the call?
- Fuck, he's a nanna.
-  So that's a yes?
- You having dinner, babe?
Did you make the fucking call?
Oh, we are good, mate.
Oh...
My dad had
a caravan like this. Ugh!
Ooh, and what
do we have here, huh?
"Our Penny Lane,
we are so very proud of you!
"Love always, Nan and Pop.
Kiss kiss!"
That's very touching.
- What the fuck are you doin'?
- What?
Special edition war champagne
from Grandpa's secret stash?
Settle in, molls.
Might be a big one.
Oh, for fuck's sake, Angus.
So this is my
grandparents' beach house
and it's kind of,
like, a really big part
of mychildhood.
And even though
we were locals,
we spent, like,
every school holidays--
Oi!
Aren't you a little old
for a teddy?
No. Um...
No, it's a security object
for emotional comfort.
Anyway!
I was the first one to
move away and be independent
'cause I've always felt--
I have no shame holding her.
And, you know,
she's obviously a tiger.
Can you shut up?!
Grrr!
- Thank you.
-  Who's that?
No-one.
Who... who is that?
- She's not bad.
-  She's alright!
Fuckin' cheese and rice!
Do you know her?
She's my... cousin,
Penny Lane.
Not blood relative?
Can you set me up with her?
Hey, back off, mate!
I saw her first.
Get fucked. I saw her first
and I asked first.
It doesn't matter
who asked first!
She's 16 in that photo!
- Huh?
-  What?
I said she's 16 in that photo.
So?
But, hey...
I guess you do like teenagers.
How old are you anyway?
And why were you in jail?
Right, let's go!
Oh, come on.
At least finish the bottles!
What was I in jail for?
Come on.
What wasI in jail for?
Was I... What was...
Oh, what was I in jailfor?
I think a little bit
of wee came out.
Ah, fuck...
For being a very naughty boy.
- Big man, ya wanna rack up?
-  Nah.
- No, no, no, we gotta go.
- Ooh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Come on!
We won't tell Daddy.
-  We know you won't.
- Come on.
Come on, Nanna.
Get in here. Fuckin' just one.
- Just one, then we go.
- Yes! Yes, let's go!
You beauty!
How about you cheeky girls,
huh? You ever had gear before?
Well, I won't say no.
Thank you!
- Mm-mm-mm!
- Give it here. Give it here.
Give it here. Now!
Fuckin' idiot.
Oh!
Sorry about that, ladies.
"
by Divinyls plays over stereo]
♪ I knew when I met you
I would not forget you ♪
♪ I knew I had to
let you know, oh ♪
♪ I knew that it was you who
did it with your voodoo ♪
♪ I'm never gonna
let you go, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, no
♪ Never let you go ♪
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
- Whoo-ahh!
- ♪ Never let you go...
Nah, nah, nah!
So sad!
♪ Never let you go...
Rodo! Rodo!
♪ I'm never gonna
let you go, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh...
-  I got wood!
♪ Never let you go ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh...
- Oh, fuck!
- ♪ Never let you go...
- Huh!
- ♪ Oh, oh...
- Ow!
♪ Never let you... ♪
Ohh!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, baby!
Mm, come here, baby.
♪ You play the game,
tryin' to explain ♪
♪ Your love is tame ♪
♪ But you're like a dog ♪
♪ Out on the prowl ♪
♪ And I adore it
♪ You pour your love
with just a touch... ♪
We've gotta get 'em out.
There's no way Kat's leaving.
♪ Fillin' me up
until I drown... ♪
Unless she wants to.
Why would she?
Hey, Angus!
Mm?
How did Kat get
such a hot guy like you?
Because she is really
punching above her weight.
Fuck you!
You're not the first girl
to say that to me.
♪ You come alive
♪ When we're alone...
♪ You keep me warm... ♪
Maybe you're more my type.
♪ And I just love you
even more... ♪
Maybe I am.
Or maybe it's time
you guys left.
What do you think, Kat?
♪ You drive me crazy
every night... ♪
Don't want the night
getting out of hand.
♪ You sexy thing
♪ Don't ever take
your love away... ♪
Anything could happen.
♪ 'Cause there's a fire...
Hey, hey, what the fuck?!
Give me that.
Dickhead!
Think the party's over, guys.
Or maybe
it's just starting.
Hmm.
Ooh!
Who wants to meet
this hot bitch? Oh!
What?
She's down there,
off her tits.
You're full of it.
Are you fucking serious?
Follow me, pussy cat.
If you do this,
I will kill you.
- Oh, you're so tough.
- This isn't a game, Kat.
Oh, but it is, and I just won.
Ah!
Oh, Jesus Christ...
Hello, sweetheart!
-  Get out!
- Ooh-ooh-ooh!
It's been a long time
since I've seen
a hot chick like this.
- Get out! Get the fuck out!
- What did you give her?
She's going
nowhere fast, baby.
Look at the pins
on her. Have a look.
- Let's get a better look!
- Don't touch her!
Ooh!
I told you she's crazy.
Settle down.
Ohh!
Let's get some fresh air,
shall we?
No! Please!
Get your fucking
hands off her!
Put her down!
Put her down
right fucking now!
- You wanna stay good tonight?
-  Don't touch her!
You sit down and
you don't say a fuckin' word.
-  Put her down!
- Ohh!
♪ Da-da, da-da, da, da! Oh! ♪
♪ She's just a girl
who can't say no! ♪
What the fuck are you doin'?!
Don't fuckin' touch me!
-  Baby!
- Nup.
Yeah, yeah, nah, nah, nah.
Not happening, Rodowsky.
-  Penny, I'm coming!
- Fuck off! Get fucked!
Keep them here.
You're fuckin' dead! Arggh!
Nanna, cover your eyes!
Fuck's sake.
Rodowsky, get in the car.
- No way.
-  Nah, mate, I'm out.
And if I'm out, you're out,
you piss-weak little suck-up!
Hey! If we leave Angus alone,
we're fucked.
The old man'll kill us.
It's not the first time.
Just shut it and wait it out!
We don't have a choice.
It's nothin' to do with us.
-  Fuckin'...!
-  Penny!
Shut up!
Penny!
Oh, you are
fuckin' gorgeous.
Where have you been
hiding her, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, you like that,
don't you?
-  Penny!
-  Huh?
Just won't quit.
What is wrong with you?
You're so pathetic.
Oh, yeah? You really wanna
tell me how pathetic I am?
Arggh!
No!
Told ya to sit down.
Give me the knife.
Photos!
I'm gonna kill you!
Great party!
Oh, yeah,
that's a good girl.
That's a good girl.
Come on, come on.
Come on, fuckin'...
Come on. Fuckin' come on!
Come on. Be a good girl.
Fuck! Come on!
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
- Toilet.
- Piss off.
Oh, I'm gonna shit myself.
Oh-- Merrick?
Yeah, just fuckin' take her.
Fuck.
Come on.
Are you kidding me?
Do you really think
I want to see you shit?
Hmph! Yeah, you're not
so desperate now, are ya?
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Guess she's not that pretty.
Oh, my God!
-  No.
-  Shh, shh, shh, shh!
Hey, youse
havin' fun without me?
Stay.
You watch 'em.
Oh, fuck...
Fuck! Ow! Arggh!
She's always been
such a fuckin' bitch.
Get in the car.
And don't fuckin'
put my boyfriend
back in jail, you got it?
You slag moll.
And don't you dare
tell your fuckin' mum.
She won't believe you anyway.
You, shut it!
Angus, get in the car.
You don't know the mouth
on her. She'll dob for sure.
Just get in the fuckin' car
and we go now.
- Call the cops.
- Where are you going?
I'm getting help.
Stay with Penny.
Fuck!
Toni!
Fuckin' Toni!
Where's Rodowsky?
She's fuckin'
gonna tell the cops!
She's gonna
fuckin' tell everyone!
- Fuckin' moll.
- Get the fuck back.
She's going to the...
bottle shop.
The bottle shop?
Go and get her.
-  No.
- What do you mean, no?
There's no keys, mate.
He fuckin' nicked it!
Rodowsky!
-  What?
-  Where have you been?
She hit me
in the fuckin' head!
Tell me you're kidding.
- I'm fuckin' bleeding!
-  Just go and get her.
-  Who?
- The grumpy one!
From the bottle shop!
Go and get her!
Oh, fuck!
-  You're going back in.
- Shut the fuck up.
She's been a fuckin' dobber
her whole life.
We're all fucked. She's gonna
tell fuckin' everyone!
She fuckin' always sets me up.
Shut up. Shut up. Yeah?
-  She lies about me.
- Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
'Cause she's
so fuckin' perfect,
blondie little fuck.
There.
Better?
She'll never open
her pretty little mouth again.
Now will you
do me the kindness
of shutting the fuck up?!
-  You! Go! Now!
-  Alright.
- Please!
- I'm on it.
Oh!
You killed her!
Well, this never happened.
We were never here.
Got it? Got it? Look at me.
I need to see you get it. Yes?
Got it? Let me see you get it.
- We were never here. Yes?
-  Okay, I got it, baby.
-  Yes? Hm? Huh?
-  Got it, baby.
-  Uh-uh-uh!
-  I won't see you later!
End her there,
but if you find yourself
incapable of that,
bring her back here
and I will deal with it.
I'll kill her myself.
Good man! Ha-ha!
No bodies, no evidence! Whoo!
- Whoo!
-  Yeah, baby!
Fucking go! Go!
Go, go, go, go!
Mm-mm!
Wasn't there
another one?
The librarian.
I'll do it.
I've got another
comfort animal!
It's an eel!
'Tis slippery!
Ah...
Hmm.
Oh, get fucked.
Fuck.
Shit.
Oh!
Oh, for fuck's sake!
You are kidding.
What fuckin' cockhead
leaves its keys in the car?
Shit.
Hmm.
Mm...
I can smell
ya fuckin' hairy taco.
Where are ya,
ya bitch?
Huh.
Hmph.
Where are you, you dickhead?
This isn't gonna end well!
You! Arggh!
Oh, you bitch!
Oh, you're kidding.
Hey!
You're as fucked
as your friend!
Penny Lane is dead!
Penny Lane is dead.
- Ugh!
- You fuckin' come here.
You fuckin' bitch!
You look me in the eye,
you fuckin' bitch!
Huh! Come here, you fuckin'...
No, no!
- Huh!
- You fuckin'...
You...!
Penny.
- Get inside.
- Fuckin' charming.
Oh! Where are you goin', huh?
Jesus, what fuckwit did this?
That's rooted.
You're a fuckin' idiot.
Sorry, what?
- Did you make the call?
- She fucked it before I could.
There are people expecting us!
Very important people.
Remember?
You think the cops
aren't watching ya, mate?
I got 50 grand of gear and
some just-out-of-jail fucktard
whackin' little girls
in the front fuckin' lawn.
Onelittle girl.
One is enough, cockhead.
Don't fucking call him that!
Well, you can just
shut the fuck up.
You forgetting who I am? Hmm?
You mean your daddy, don't ya?
Who's your dad? Is he famous?
What, you seriously
don't know who his dad is?
You're just sucking his dick
because of his incredible
fuckin' personality, are ya?
His dad is the only reason
he doesn't get cock-punched
every time he opens
his fuckin' mouth.
You saying I can't
handle myself?
I'm saying your daddy
cleans up after you
like a baby with
a shitty fuckin' nappy
and everybody knows it
except for you.
You've got balls, dickhead.
But clearly no fuckin' brains.
Fuck, I had one fuckin' job!
Just go there, drop off,
come back, with you,
without the whole thing
fucking up.
Angus?
Failed at fuckin' babysitting.
Well, has he been
on the telly?
If you don't calm down,
you're gonna have
another little one
of your heart attacks.
I'll make you a hot chocolate.
I don't want
a fuckin' hot chocolate!
Relax! Relax, Nanna Merri.
Everything is fine!
Listen, we wait for Rodowsky,
then we do a little house
cleaning, and then we leave.
Huh?
So we're a couple
of hours late.
We had, er... car trouble.
Could happen to anybody.
That can't be helped.
No-one's none the wiser--
I was in the newspaper
once when I was a kid.
This photographer came
to our school and--
Shut the fuck up!
You stupid bitch!
They're gonna make this
all my fuckin' fault,
just you wait.
Why? Why?
Why? I don't understand.
Why couldn't you
leave me alone?
Shit. Fuck.
Kat.
This has gone too far.
Okay?
You've gotta get away
from them. Let me help you.
You do know you're
a bit mental, don't you?
Just come with me.
He's gonna hurt you
if you stay.
- He'd never fuckin' hurt me.
-  Okay.
You're better than this, Kat.
Oh, sweet little Amy.
I'm really not.
Kat?!
Where the fuck is she?
Hmm, hmm...
Yeah?
Where?!
Fuckin', "Oh, here!"
Like I know exact...
Oh-ho, you are
fuckin' kidding me!
Bye-bye, Amy.
Hey, can I have a go?
- Can I have a go?
- No!
Oh, come on. Please!
Hey, Amy, where are
you going, huh?
- Stop!
-  "Stop!"
Hey, mousey,
you forgot something!
- Oh-ho-ho!
- Come on!
Hey. Would you like a push,
little girl, hm?
No! Get away!
Alright, little girl.
Stop it!
"Ooh, stop it!"
Oh, there is a fire in you
and I like it!
Come on!
Oh, Amy, you fuckin' loser.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
This little piggy
went to market.
should've stayed home.
This little piggy
snorted speed.
And this little piggy
really wants some more.
But Amy little piggy went,
"Wee, wee, wee, wee!"
all the way...
...fucking nowhere.
Got a surprise for ya, Amy.
Do you wanna see it?
- Don't rape me.
- Ooh!
You hoping for a little bit,
were you? Dirty moll.
You're disgusting.
What did you say to me?
I said you're disgusting.
And you are small
and you are nothing.
And I hate you.
And I fucking hate
what you did to my friend.
Do you really want to know
what I was in jail for? Hmm?
Oh, fuck.
Where'd you get a fuckin' gun?
None of your business.
- Where's Amy?
- She's having a lie-down.
Why?
She's dead, you moron.
- What?
- Ugh!
What is it now?
You didn't even like her!
Maybe I'd like some attention
for a change.
You'd like some attention
for a change?
I'll give you
some attention!
You want a little bit
of attention?
Nothin' like a gunshot
to keep things
low-key, you dumb fuck.
Where's the girl?
She hit her head.
Go and get her.
Keep an eye out
for the teddy. Yeah?
We gotta take out
the trash, right?
Take that off.
Come on.
Take it off, take it off.
♪ You like it better
with my lipstick off ♪
♪ You got a taste
and you can't get enough ♪
♪ Against the wall ♪
♪ Oh, I won't move ♪
♪ You know you like it
with the top down low ♪
♪ The air gets thick and
now we're good to go ♪
♪ Let's take a ride ♪
♪ Oh, I am feeling alive
♪ I know it, I feel it ♪
♪ You want this,
you need it this time ♪
♪ You got it, so take it... ♪
You're a bad boy, Angus.
Oh, you've got no idea.
♪ You pull me closer
when I start to run... ♪
Baby, I...
I gotta tell you something.
Yeah, just a sec. Come on.
I just reckon you're, like,
the coolest guy ever
and fuckin' I just...
Mn-mn.
Angus, baby, I fuckin' love--
Mn-mn!
♪ I know it, I feel it ♪
♪ You want this,
you need it this time ♪
♪ You got it, so take it,
I need it ♪
♪ We'll make this
our night... ♪
How was it?
We're still going, aren't we?
I mean with Penny.
Like, how was it
compared to me?
It's okay.
It happens to guys
all the time--
♪ Just one taste
and we couldn't stop ♪
♪ You like it better
with my lipstick off... ♪
Ugh...
Penny?
Penny.
Hey, Penny. Hey...
Penny, come back.
Hey...
Oh, my God, Penny.
Hey. Hey, Penny?
Shit.
What the fuck was...
- You stupid fuckin'...
-  Who did it?
You listen to me.
Well, check out
fuckin' Houdini!
Mn-mn-mn-mn.
Where's all this blood
coming from?
Who did it?
Where's Rodowsky?
Jesus, you get
your rags?
Eugh!
Oh! You did that?
I'm impressed.
Rodowsky!
I got about 30 minutes
until I bleed out.
Yeah, and we got a crapload
of gear in that boot.
Rodowsky!
He's at the bottle shop.
Bottle shop? You see Nick?
Did you see Nick?
Did you
see Nick?
I don't think he can
drive back, but.
And why is that, sweetheart?
You can't drive without feet.
That's actually pretty...
Wait! Wait!
I wanna kill her.
Ugh!
And one!
And two.
And...
...three!
Ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding!
She's outta here!
Oh, yeah, she's
a real fuckin' winner, mate.
Ah!
Huh!
Scrag!
Fuckin' dyke!
Oh, just give it
a fuckin' rest, will ya?
Fuckin' ugly scrag!
I do not know why you are
bothering with that thing.
Ugh!
It's not for me.
Well, you can't
bring anyone here.
Look at the place, mate.
It's a mess.
There's glass. What if
somebody hurts themself?
Slut!
Look!
She's still goin'!
My daughter's waitin' for me.
I don't think you two
are going to make it, hm?
You know,
when it comes to chicks,
there's five types of crazy,
and you're all of them.
Oh, fuck off, Angus.
Can I tell you a secret?
I fuckin' love you.
You're such a chicken.
I'm not a chicken.
I'm just saying, like,
what happens when people...
Shh.
Mn-mn.
Everyone is gonna say
I turned you into a lesbian.
Yeah, that's right.
But I always said
you were very...
very...
...clever.
You brought him here for me?
You expecting someone?
Oh, Jesus...
Six types of crazy.
Amy?
Uh! Uh-uh! Uh-uh!
Shut up. Come here.
Open your mouth.
Come on. Open it!
Kat. What the fuck?
Hi, Nick.
What happened to you?
God, I haven't
seen you since...
What, that day in court?
Oh, my God.
I... I barely remember that.
Yeah, well, I won't forget it.
Where's all this blood
coming from?
Where are the girls?
Where's Penny and Toni?
Their cars are here.
Get off my bike.
Be honest - do you reckon
we would've worked out
if Penny hadn't talked
all that shit about me?
Look, I thought they were
having a girls' night in,
but... but if not,
I'm out of here.
Nick! Run!
- We're playing a game...
- The fuck have you done now?
Nick, don't... don't go
in there! Nick, ple... No!
Shut up!
What the fuck?!
Go, Nick!
Run! Run, Nick!
Nick, don't stop!
Stop!
-  Stop!
-  Don't touch me!
-  Come on, you bastard!
-  Fuck off!
No!
No! No!
Nick! Don't hurt him!
Don't hurt him! Stop!
Angus, stop!
Stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
Please, stop.
You one of those
hero types, mate?
-  Stop it.
- Oh, shit, no.
Smart kid.
Not that smart.
Oh, you'll laugh later.
Stop hitting yourself,
stop hitting yourself!
Ah, you little fuck.
- I love this shirt.
- I want to go.
I think you liked him!
And now there's
only one bullet.
I said I want to go home.
One bullet for
the crazy bitch, hey?
What did you say?
Redheads.
Complete fuckin' lunatics.
That bloke was pretty shit,
wasn't he, hey?
Bit of an anticlimax, really.
A bit like fuckin' her, mate.
Whoa!
Ooh! Easy there,
tiger!
-  Fuck you! Fuck you!
-  No? Really? Fuck me?
No, no, no, no!
You are not your cousin, baby!
-  Screw you!
-  Really? Screw me?
Hey, know what'll fix this?
You know what'll fix this?
A little bit of speed!
Come with me. Here we go.
Mmm, look at this.
Get it up there, yes. Nice.
And in the gums, huh?
Isn't that better, baby? Huh?
Yeah?
Fuck me? Fuck me, huh?
Fuck me? Fuck me?
Oh, Kitty Kat, fuck me.
I just told you, my darling.
I just told you. Come here.
Come here, come here, come
here. It's okay, it's okay.
I just told you.
It's not gonna work out
between you and I.
Okay? It is not going to
work out between you and I.
Fuck me,
women are crazy!
Huh?
Oh, oh, oh!
Whoa.
Consider yourself fucked.
Sen-fuckin'-sational.
No!
No, my baby!
-  Knife.
-  Do something!
Call an ambulance!
Do something!
It's gone!
Angus, your dick is gone!
He thought
you were his friend!
You are such
a backstabber and--
Ugh!
- Come on, moll.
- Arggh!
- Get up!
- Oh!
You know only one of us
is coming out of this.
You killed her, you ugly dog!
Arggh!
No-one's gonna love you now.
Toni! Fuck you!
Open the door,
you fuckin' coward!
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you!
You stupid moll.
My tooth's
fuckin' gone, bitch!
You killed my boyfriend!
He loved me!
You're just so fuckin' jealous
'cause someone I fuckin' loved
loved me back.
I watched him kill her.
I watched him
kill her.
How could you?
Guess it was my childhood.
I fuckin' hate you.
Sorry, what was that?
Get off!
Oh, you're fuckin' dead, moll!
Josh!
Fuck.
What the fuck happened to you?
- Kat.
- Kat? What the fuck?
Where's Nick?
Are you serious?
- The knife.
- Fuckin' hell.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
She's still here.
- Where's Nick?
- We've gotta go.
- Now!
- No, Toni, where's Nick?!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
Oi, lezzo!
It didn't need
to be like this!
This was your choice.
You just can't take a joke.
Three out of three sluts.
Not bad.
Huh!
No!
Arggh!
No! No!
So how's your night been?
Oh...
Winning feels good.
Ooh.
So I guess
you're gonna die now.
Oh, you're not afraid
of heights, are you?
God, I think I'm doing
this right. Jesus.
Here she is - Miss Australia!
Not the happy ending you
were after, huh, tough chick?
No driving into the sunrise
for this dumb bitch!
Oh, no!
And the winner is...
God. Hurry up and die,
for fuck's sake.
The winner is me.
Arggh!
Not today, loser.
Come on, come on.
Toni!
Oh...
Oh, my God. Oh!
Hey.
You're alive.
I really fuckin' love you.
I know.
I really fuckin' love you too.
Fuck you!
Fuck me?
Did you just say fuck me?!
Oh!
Fuck you!
Where were we?
♪ Big girls, hey, hey,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, uh-oh, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, oh, oh,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Now we are big girls ♪
♪ We're gonna
face this break-up ♪
♪ And now we are
grown-up people... ♪
We good?
Yeah. We're always
fuckin' good.
I hate you!
Ya molls!
Shut up!
♪ I remember the days
when we thought ♪
♪ Our love would never die ♪
♪ And now we are big girls
♪ We're gonna
face this break-up ♪
♪ And now we are
grown-up people ♪
♪ Well, we know
that we won't make up, but ♪
♪ I remember the times
when we could laugh ♪
♪ And we could rock hard
♪ And I remember the days
when we thought ♪
♪ Our love would never die
♪ Big girls,
face this break-up ♪
♪ Big girls, hey, hey,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, uh-oh, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, oh, oh,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, hey, hey, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, oh, oh,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, hey, hey, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, oh, oh,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, hey, hey, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, oh, oh,
we won't make up, no, no ♪
♪ Big girls, hey, hey, face
this break-up, good girl ♪
♪ Big girls, bigger girls,
bigger girls, big girls ♪
♪ Big girls, big girls ♪
♪ Big girls,
big girls, big girls ♪
♪ Big girls, big girls,
big girls ♪
♪ Big girls,
big girls, big girls ♪
♪ Hey, hey, big girls ♪
♪ Big girls,
oh, oh, big girls ♪
♪ Hey, hey, oh, oh,
big girls ♪
♪ Hey, hey,
oh, oh, big girls ♪
♪ Bigger girls, bigger girls,
bigger girls, big girls! ♪
Captions produced by
Access Media Pty Ltd